本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
我想早点完成圣诞购物
I like to get my christmas shopping done early.
你有什么符合节日精神的商品吗
Do you have anything that's in the spirit of the season?
呃  这些水晶如何
Uh, how about these crystals?
哈哈  看起来就像碎玻璃
Ha ha! Looks like broken glass.
怎么  你是警察吗
What are you, a cop?
噢  这是什么新玩意儿
Oh! What is that new thing?
斯坦叔公  我们能去餐厅吗
Grunkle stan. Can we go to the diner?
我们好饿饿饿
We're huuungry.
饿饿饿
Huuuungry.
当然可以  只要等这个笨蛋决定好买什么就行
Yeah, sure. Soon as this yahoo makes up his mind.
这东西有其他动物的款式吗
You have this in another animal?
我乐意把他锁在房里  如果你们同意的话
I'm fine locking him inside if you are.
美洲狮衬衫  美洲豹衬衫
Puma shirt, panther shirt.
美洲狮衬衫
Puma shirt...
美洲豹衬衫
Panther shirt.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
■
时间轴： shortcut
翻译： sarina
■
校订： WaitinZ
后期： WaitinZ  leland
怪诞小镇  第一季第六集
Gravity Falls  S01E06  Dipper vs. Manliness
走开
Shoo!
讨厌鬼
Git!
咖啡  咖啡
Coffee! Coffee!
开始  开始
Go! Go! Go! Go!
懒苏珊  你就是我的一缕阳光
Lazy Susan! There's my little ray of sunshine!
你昨天哪儿去啦
Where we you  yesterday?
我被公交车撞到了
I got hit by a bus!
哈哈哈哈  太好笑啦
Ha ha ha ha! Hilarious!
谢谢
Thank you.
你们允许买半份  是吧
You do split plates, right?
也许吧
Maybe.
眨眼
Wink.
好  那我们要七号餐的四分之一
Great! We'll all split one-fourth of the number seven,
还有给这位小姐一份免费沙拉
Plus a free salad dressing for the lady
跟给这位男孩一小碟番茄酱
And a small plate of ketchup for the boy.
斯坦叔公  我想吃煎饼
But grunkle stan, I want pancakes.
那些昂贵的面粉制品吗
With the fancy flour they use these days?
你以为我是钱做的吗
What am I, made of money?
玩游戏
赢免费煎饼！
测试你的男子气概
别担心  伙计们  煎饼包在我身上
Don't worry, guys. Pancakes are on me.
我要挑战男子气概测试器  给大家赢煎饼
I'm gonna win some by beating that manliness tester.
-男子气概测试器  -挑战
-Manliness tester? -Beating?
他说  他说他要
He says--he says he's--
干嘛  有什么好笑
What? What's so funny?
迪普  无意冒犯  但是你可不是有男子气概的曼宁顿
No offense, Dipper, but you're not exactly manly Mannington.
喂  我也是有男子气概的  曼尼
Hey! I am too manly... Manny,
或者是你说的其他东西
Or whatever it is you said.
面对现实吧  孩子
Look, face the music, kid.
你没有肌肉  你闻起来像婴儿卫生纸
You got no muscles, you smell like baby wipes,
而且我们不要忘了上星期二的  那个事件
And let's not forget last Tuesday's... Incident.
迪斯科女孩  快过来  那女孩就是你
Disco girl, coming through, that girl is you.
别进来  别进来
Don't come in, don't come in.
你在听冰岛女子流行音乐组合巴芭的歌
You were listening to girly Icelandic pop sensation Babba?
不  我没有  这事不重要
No, I wasn't. It's not important!
听着  伙计们  我充满阳刚气概
Look, come on, guys, I'm plenty masculine!
看到这些胸毛了吗
You see this chest hair?
-快遮住  快遮住  -太光滑太刺眼了  我的眼睛啊
-Put it away! Put it away! -So smooth! My eyes!
唉  天哪
Oh, man.
行  一点信心也不给的家人
Fine, family of little faith.
准备好食言吧
Get ready to eat your words...
还有一大碟煎饼
And a plate of delicious pancakes.
好了  迪普
All right, Dipper.
是时候用男人的方式握住这跟握杆了
Time to manhandle this... Man handle.
一  二
And a-one, and a-two...
别磨蹭了
Quit stallin'!
懦夫
中年妇女
说不过去
男人
你是个可爱的小宝贝
什么  这机器肯定是坏了
Oh, what?! This thing must be broken.
这机器完全坏了  伙计们  就像一百万岁那么老
It's totally broken, guys. It's like a million years old.
估计是没了蒸汽动力  或者
Probably ran out of steam power or--
这东西坏了  你根本不用
It's rickety, man. You shouldn't even--
好呀  每人一份煎饼
Yes! Pancakes for everyone!
我得长点胸毛  立马就要
I need to get some chest hair, and fast.
我没事  哈哈
I'm fine! Heh heh.
什么事也没有
Everything's fine.
老天  我怎么会跟那家伙是亲戚呢
Sheesh! How am I related to that?
拜托  斯坦叔公
Come on, Grunkle Stan.
我确信你内心深处也有温柔的一面
I'm sure deep down you have a soft side too.
哈  这里面除了一具冰冷  黑暗  空洞的灵魂外什么都没有
Ha! Nothing in here but a cold, dark, empty soul.
食物来啦
Food!
谢了  甜心
Thanks there, sugar pie.
我是说甜蜜黄蜂猫咪小宝贝
I mean, honey wasp kitten baby.
牛宝贝
Ba-baby cow--
哈哈  傻瓜
Ha ha! Silly!
-笨男人  -那是怎么回事
-Silly man. -What was that about?
没什么  我  呃  不想谈这个
Nothing. I, uh, don't want to talk about it.
谈什么  为什么这桌子湿了
Talk about what? Why is this table wet?
等一下
Wait just a second.
我想我知道这是怎么回事了
I think I have an idea happening here.
-你  -不
-You... -No!
-跟她  -不  别说了
-And her... -No! Stop it!
-啊  -我的老天
-Aaah! -Oh, boy.
你对懒苏珊有好感
You have a thing for lazy Susan!
你确实有温柔的一面
You do have a soft side!
但是别说出去  好吗
But k-k-keep it down, will ya?
好了好了  我承认  如果她也喜欢我  那就很好
All right. I admit it, okay? It would be nice if she liked me.
但是我已经离场很久了  而且我不知道应该从哪儿入手
But I've been out of the game for so long I wouldn't know where to start.
我是说  你瞧她  她是多么的优雅
I mean, look at her. She's so classy.
转啊  你这蠢馅饼  快转啊
Spin, ya dumb pie! Spin!
斯坦叔公
Grunkle Stan,
你是个脾气暴躁  恶心  古怪的老男人
You are a cranky, gross, weird old man.
但是我们会让懒苏珊喜欢上你的
But we will get lazy Susan to like you,
因为世上没有什么力量比这更强大了
Because nothing is stronger than the power of...
-爱的力量吗  -梅宝的力量
-Love? -Mabel.
为了胜利
To victory!
不够男人
Not manly enough.
蠢餐厅  蠢伐木工
Stupid diner! Stupid lumberjack!
不
No!
又一个消防栓坏了
Another hydrant destroyed.
真是个天大的谜题啊
It's a gosh-dang mystery!
想脱掉制服  然后围着转圈跑吗
Wanna take off our uniforms and run around in circles?
不要再读我的心思了
Quit readin' my mind.
噢  抱歉  我在找邮差
Oh, I'm sorry. I was looking for the mailman.
什么  你是说我不是雄性的男人么
Oh. What? Are you saying I'm not a male man?
（注：mailman与male man同音）
这就是你想要说的话吗
Is that what you're trying to say?
我不是男的  我不是男人
I'm not male? I'm not a man?
这就是你的暗示吗
Is that what you're getting at?
你是要哭了吗
Are you crying?
二
Two...
三
Three...
四
Four...
还是没有胸毛
No chest hair yet.
是生理因素吗  还是心理因素  其中的奥秘是什么
Is it physical? Is it mental? What's the secret?
真男人肉干
你根本不够格
你说得对  老兄  我需要帮助
You said it, brother. I need help.
看在神圣的爱的份上  快跑吧
For the love of all that's holy, run!!!!
等一下  抱歉
Wait. Sorry.
拜托不要吃我  我一星期没洗澡了
Please don't eat me! I haven't showered in like a week!
而且我瘦得只剩骨头了  还有脆骨
And I'm-- I'm like all elbows! Elbows and gristle!
你
You
要把那个吃完吗
Gonna finish that?
没有
No.
真不敢相信  半人半兽
I can't believe it. Part animal, part human.
你是牛头怪吗
Are you some kind of minotaur?
我是男牛怪
I'm a manotaur!
一半男人  一半  呃
Half man, half, uh...
一半牛
Half taur!
那么  是我引你过来的  还是
So did I, like, summon you, or...
是肉干的香味把我吸引过来的
The smell of jerky summoned me!
肉干
Jerky!
我闻到了
I smell...
感情问题
...Emotional issues.
我遇到问题了  男牛怪  有关男子气概的问题
I got problems, manotaur. Man-related problems.
是这样的  我的亲叔公管我叫懦夫
Well, my own uncle called me a wimp,
而且我挑战男子气概测试游戏算是彻底失败了
And I kinda flunked this manliness video game thing... Hmm...
喂  那个  你看起来挺有男人味儿的
Hey! You know, you seem pretty manly.
或许你能给我点提示
Maybe you could give me some pointers?
嗯  那好
Hmm. Very well.
爬到我的背毛上  孩子
Climb atop my back hair, child.
呃  好吧
Uh, okay.
来啊  来啊
Yes! Yes!
伙计  小心啊
Dude, watch out!
这地方太棒了
This place is amazing!
小矮人住在树里
The gnomes live in the trees,
美人鱼住在海里  因为他们是废物
The mer-people live in the water-- 'cause they're losers!--
但是我们男牛人住在充满男人味的山洞里
But we manotaurs crash in the man cave!
野兽们  我给你们带来了
Beasts! I have brought you...
一个毫毛不长的小孩
A hairless child!
嗨
'Sup?
他们是  扑鼻牛  荷尔蒙牛  粘液牛
This is, uh, Pubitaur, Testosteraur, Pituitaur,
我是大胆牛
And I'm Chutzpaur.
-那你是   -我叫迪普
And you are... My name's Dipper.
太弱了
Weak!
那个  呃  破坏者
The, uh, Destructor?
-嗯  这就好多了  -有进步
-Yeah, that's better. -An improvement, yeah.
破坏者迪普希望我们教他
Dipper the destructor wants us to teach him
刚阳之气的秘诀
The secrets to our manliness!
我需要你们的帮助  看这里  伙计们  看看这里
I need your help. Look at this, guys-- look at this!
我必须跟高级委员会商讨一下
I must confer with the high council.
那个  要教他我们的刚阳秘诀吗
So, teach him our man secrets, or what?
他是人类  我不喜欢他
He's a human. I don't like him.
我不喜欢你的脸
I don't like your face!
我喜欢这些家伙
I like these guys.
好了  斯坦叔公
Okay, Grunkle Stan.
欢迎来到你生命中剩余部分的第一天
Welcome to the first day of whatever is left of your life!
首先拍一张改造前的照片
First a "before" picture.
我从来不会错失拍剪贴簿照片的好时机
I never miss a scrapbook-ortunity.
海誓山盟啊  珍贵记忆啊
deedley-dum, mem-ories
我们从角色扮演开始
Let's start out with some role-playing.
苏斯扮演懒苏珊
Soos will play lazy Susan.
我就像女人一样温柔
I'm soft like a woman.
斯坦叔公  向我展示你怎么接近女人的
Grunkle Stan, show me how you approach a woman.
记住这是一个安全  客观的环境
Remember this is a safe, non-judgmental environment.
我会在这边  分数范围由一到十地给你评分
I'll just be right off to the side judging you on a scale from one to ten.
我能借点钱吗
Can I borrow some money?
这事情会比我想象得难办
This is gonna be harder than I thought.
经过一轮拳打脚踢
After a lot of punching,
我们决定拒绝你希望学习我们的刚阳秘诀的请求
We have decided to deny your request to learn our manly secrets.
拒绝
Denied!
好吧  行  我能接受
Okay, fine. That's okay with me.
显然你们认为训练我太艰难了
Obviously you guys think it would be too hard to train me.
也许你们没有足够的男子气概去尝试
Maybe you're not man enough to try.
什么
Huh?!!!
不够男人
Not man enough?!
破坏者
Destructor...
不够男人
Not man enough?!!!
他不是这个意思
He didn't mean it.
我有三条Y染色体  六个喉结
I have three y chromosomes, six adam's apples,
健壮的胸肌  还有拳头一样的乳头
Pecs on my abs, and fists for nipples!
在我看来你像是害怕教我怎么做男人
Seems to me you're scared to teach me how to be a man.
喂  你们听到了吗  这声音听起来像
Hey, do you guys hear that? It sounds like...
噢  真奇怪
Oh, that's weird.
这听起来就像  就像一群懦夫
Is that--that sounds like-- yeah, a bunch of chickens!
我觉得这事情很古怪
I feel all weird.
他在用什么脑瓜魔法
He's using some sort of brain magic!
经过第二轮商议后
After a second round of deliberation,
我们决定帮助你成为一个男人
We have decided to help you become a man!
男人  男人  男人  男人
Man! Man! Man! Man!
太好了  谢谢你们
Great! Thanks, guys.
无论如何  我都不会让你们失望的
Whatever it is, I will not let you down.
成为男人就是要战胜恐惧
Being a man is about conquering your fears.
你的第一项男人挑战
For your first man task,
你必须把拳头伸进痛苦之洞里面
You must plunge your fist into the pain hole!
什么
The what?
痛苦之洞  失命之洞
Pain hole, schmain ho--
你们确定这真的有必要吗
Are you sure this is really necessary?
你想成为男人  对吧
You wanna be a man, don't you?
男人  男人  男人
Man! Man! Man!
好吧  我们来试试把你的内在美展现在外表上吧
All right. Let's try to get that inner beauty on the outside.
笑得再用力一点
Smile harder.
再用力点
Harder!
完美
Perfect.
-苏斯  -干啥啊  小鬼头
-Soos! -What's up, hambone?
你感觉如何
What do you think?
哎  看来得要一些神奇培训音乐的帮助
Ohh. This is going to take some really great training music.
训练金曲
当老虎咆哮时
When the tiger roars
当山崩地裂时
And the mountain cries
你必须执着于梦
You gotta dream the dream
你必须赢得奖励
You gotta win the prize
你必须不远万里
You gotta go the miles
你必须面对挑战
You gotta face the trials
别挠了
永远不要忽略你看到的东西
Never lose sight of the sights you see
眼神交流
你必须相信自己的信仰
You got believe your beliefs are real
现在你正从消防栓里喝水
Now you're drinking from a fire hydrant
教导你的叔公如何穿腹带
Teach your uncle how to wear a cummerbund
现在你要跳过一个疯狂的山峡
Now you're gonna jump a crazy gorge
继续替毛茸茸的叔公刮毛
Keep on shavin' that hairy uncle
我不知道这部分到底发生了什么事
I don't really know what what's happening in this part
心在燃烧  心中之火
Your heart's on fire and the fire is in your heart
谁想替我搓背
Who wants to rub this on my back?
伙计们  我只想告诉你们刚刚的几个小时实在是
Guys, I just want to say that these last few hours have been--
我觉得我真的成长了一些
I feel like there's really been some growth.
我也成长了
I have a growth!
格拉科  你今天太搞笑了
Glark, you are hilarious today!
你们能一直保护着我
It's just you guys took me under your wing
-而且一直支持我  -别说了
-And have just been so supportive. -Oh, stop.
不  你知道吗  你们确实很棒
No, you know what? You really have been.
我觉得我终于变成男人了
I feel like I'm finally becoming a man here.
还没有  破坏者
Not yet, destructor.
还有最后一个挑战
One final task remains.
-喂  别这样  -你才是
-Hey, quit it! -You quit it!
最可怕的挑战
The deadliest trial of all.
我已经经历了四十九个挑战
I've survived forty-nine other trials.
不管是什么  都放马过来
Whatever it is, bring it on!
好
Yeah!
棒小伙
有请我们的领袖  领头牛
Behold our leader... Leaderaur!
他是最老的  还是最有智慧的  还是
Is he the oldest, or wisest, or...
你好啊  年轻
Greetings, young--
不是  他只是贡品  这个才是领头牛
Nah, he's just the offering. That is leaderaur.
你  你想当男人
You! You wish to be man?
好
Yeah!
那你必须做出点英勇事迹来
Then you must do heroic act.
去最高的山岭
Go to highest mountain...
然后带回多头熊的
...And bring back head of...
脑袋
The multi-bear.
多头熊  是一种熊吗
The multi-bear? That some sort of bear?
他是我们不共戴天的敌人
He's our sworn enemy.
只要征服了他  你的男人转变就会完成
Conquer him and your mansformation will be complete.
征服他  我不确定啊
Conquer? I don't know, man.
破坏者  这是你的吗
Destructor! Is this yours?
不  哈哈  我不知道这是谁的
Uh, no. Ha ha! I-- I don't know whose that is.
我只是把它借过来了  这是朋友的  不是我的
I was just borrowing it. It's a friend's. Not mine.
这事有点古怪
I don't know about this.
我要征服多头熊
I shall conquer the multi-bear!
我没事
I'm okay.
我来找你了  多头熊
I'm comin' for you, multi-bear.
好了  斯坦叔公
Okay, Grunkle Stan.
你开始时是这个样子
You started like this,
但是你变成了
But you became...
我现在可以挠痒痒了吗
Can I scratch myself now?
不  不  不  不
No! No, no, no!
你衬衫上的是呕吐物吗
Is that throw-up on your shirt?
我不知道要怎么回答这问题
I don't know how to answer that.
面对现实吧  梅宝  你叔公没救了
Face it, mabel, your uncle's unfixable.
就好像餐厅的那个旋转馅饼车
Like that spinning pie trolley thing in the diner.
斯坦叔公  跟我来
Grunkle Stan, come with me!
把你的裤子留在家里
And leave your pants at home.
高兴至极
With pleasure!
多头熊到底是什么东西
What is a multi-bear?
哦那就是多头熊
Oh that's a multi-bear.
熊头们  安静
Bear heads-- silence!
孩子  你来这里干什么
Child, why have you come here?
多头熊  我来取你的头
Multi-bear, I seek your head!
呃  其中一个头  你好像有  有六个头
Er, one of them, anyway. There's like, what, six? Six heads?
这太可笑了  马上离开不然就死
This if foolish! Leave now or die!
那就顺其自然了
So be it.
真正的男人绝不会心慈手软
A real man shows no mercy!
哎  好吧  战士
Ohh. Very well, warrior.
但是你能应允这个神奇野兽的最后一个请求吗
But will you grant a magical beast one last request?
呃  好吧
Uh, okay.
我希望听着我最喜欢的歌曲死去
I wish to die listening to my favorite song.
带子已经在里面了  你只要按任何一个
Tape is already in there. You can just hit any--
对对  就是这样
Yeah, yeah, that's it
你听冰岛流行组合巴芭的歌
You listen to Icelandic pop group Babba?
我喜欢巴芭
I-I love Babba.
我以为我是唯一一个
I thought I was the only one.
所有的男牛人都取笑我
All the manotaurs make fun of me
因为我熟知《迪斯科女孩》这首歌的每一句歌词
Because I know all the words to the song Disco Girl.
-哦  你是指  迪斯科女孩  -快过来
-Oh, you mean... disco girl, -coming through.
那女孩就是你  噢噢  噢噢
That girl is you, oh-oh, oh-oh.
哈哈哈  这真是太好了
Hahaha, this is crazy!
终于有人能理解
Finally, someone who-- who understands that--
噢对了  我猜我应该杀你  不然我就永远无法成为男人
Oh, yeah. I guess I'm supposed to kill you or I'll never be a man.
我接受我的命运
I accept my fate.
不  真的吗
No! Really?
这样对我们来说才是最好的
It's for the best.
我不会杀他的
I'm not gonna do it!
我告诉过你成为男人的代价就是取回多头熊的头
You were told the price of manhood is the multi-bear's head!
听着  领头牛
Listen, leaderaur, all right?
你也是  荷尔蒙牛  粘液牛
You too, Testosteraur, Pituitaur,
还有  我不知道  不管你的名字是什么
And--I don't know, whatever your name is.
-胡子牛  -是胡子牛
-Beardy? -It's Beardy.
你们一直告诉我想当男人就意味着要完成所有挑战
You keep telling me that being a man means doing all these tasks
而且无时无刻不用暴力解决问题
And being aggro all the time,
但是我开始觉得这些都是胡说八道
But I'm starting to think that stuff's malarkey.
你听见我了  胡说八道
You heard me. Malarkey!
所以也许我没有肌肉  身体某些部位也没有毛发
So maybe I don't have muscles or hair in certain places,
当然  当电台播放女子流行音乐时
And sure, when a girly pop song comes on the radio,
有时我会不换台继续听  因为  该死的
Sometimes I leave it on, 'cause dang it,
这些歌曲入围排行榜前四十名自有它的道理
Top 40 hits are in the top 40 for a reason,
-它们琅琅上口  -破坏者
-They're catchy! -Destructor!
你想说什么
What are you saying?
我想说多头熊是个好人
I'm saying the multi-bear is a really nice guy.
而如果你们想要我去砍他的头的话  你们就是一群坏蛋
And you're a bunch of jerks if you want me to cut off his head!
杀死多头熊  不然就永远别当男人
Kill the multi-bear, or never be a man!
那我猜我就永远不当男人了吧
Then I guess I'll never be a man.
呸  真弱
Boo! Weak!
伙计们  谁想去建点东西  然后把它摧毁
Hey, guys! Who wants to go build something and knock it down?
男人  男人  男人  男人
Man! Man! Man! Man!
男人  男人  男人  男人  男人
Man! Man! Man! Man! Man...
转啊  转啊
Spin! Spin!
懒苏珊  听我说
Lazy Susan, listen.
我知道他的外表并不好看
I know he's not much to look at,
但是你总是在餐厅修理各种东西
But you're always fixing stuff in the diner,
而如果你喜欢修理东西的话
And if you like fixing stuff,
没有东西比我的斯坦叔公更需要修理
Nothing could use more fixing than my Grunkle Stan.
而且  女人比男人长命
Also, women live longer than men,
那么你的交际圈子更小  所以你应该降低标准
So your dating pool is smaller and you should really lower your standards.
那么  懒苏珊  你觉得怎么样
So, Lazy Susan, whaddya say?
喂
Hey!
这是我的号码
Here's my number.
有空打电话给我吧
Why don't you give me a call sometime?
-真的吗  -真的
-Really? -Really!
还有  这里有些馅饼
Also, here's some pie.
我请客  给你的
On the house-- for  you!
我们成功了
We did it!
你想什么时候打电话  你想现在打吗
When are you gonna call? You want to call now?
我没有手机  我们去买部手机吧
I don't have a phone. Let's buy a phone!
我们可以用信用卡付钱  我们去办个信用卡
We can put it on a credit card! Let's get a credit card.
梅宝  让我好好享受馅饼  行吗
Mabel! Let a man enjoy his pie, huh?
迪普  是我啊  梅宝啊
Dipper! It's me, Mabel!
我正透过玻璃望着你
I'm looking at you through the glass!
就在这里  这是我的声音
Right here! This is my voice!
我正从里面跟你说话
I'm talking to you from inside!
-你看见我在  -看见了
-Didja see me through the-- -Yes.
怎么了
What's wrong?
-我不想谈这事儿  -很好
-I don't want to talk about it. -Good.
就是那些半人半牛的人跟我一起玩
It's just these half-man, half-bull humanoids were hanging out with me...
-又来了  -但是他们想要我
-Here we go. -But then they wanted me
去做一件非常艰难  可怕的事
To do this really tough, horrible thing,
但是这事儿不对  所以我拒绝了
But it just wasn't right, so I said no.
你有自己的主张  而且坚持自我
You were your own man and you stood up for yourself.
-什么  -即使没有人同意你  你仍做了正确的事
Huh? You did what was right even though no one agreed with you.
听起来挺有男人风范的  但谁知道呢
Sounds pretty manly to me, but what do I know?
等一下  我的眼睛没花吧
Wait a minute! Do my eyes deceive me?
你有一根胸毛了
You have a chest hair!
你说的对  我确实有根胸毛
You're right! I do!
哈哈  这太神奇了  我真的有胸毛了
Ha ha! This is amazing, I really do!
接招  刚阳考官  接招  粘液牛
Take that, man tester! Take that, Pituitaur!
-粘液牛  -这家伙有胸毛了
-Pituitaur? -This guy has chest hair!
剪贴簿好时机
Scrapbook-ortunity!
别担心  孩子  如果你跟我一样的话
Don't worry, kid. If you're anything like me,
还有很多毛会从那里出来的
There's more where that came from.
噢  真恶心
Ohh, gross!
我是说真的  真是太恶心了
Seriously, that's disgusting.
噢  怎么又来了
Oh, not again!
第三十六条留言
Message number thirty-six.
嗨  帅哥
Hey, handsome!
是我  懒苏珊  打电话来问好  嗨
It's me, Lazy Susan, calling to say hi! Hi.
我的猫也想打个招呼  说嗨  唐纳德
My cats also want to say hi, say hi, Donald.
很好  斯亚妮  你说嗨
Good. Cianey, you say hi.
猫脸先生  现在轮到你说
Mr. Catface, now it's your turn to say...
猫脸先生  好吧  记得回我电话  记得啊
Mr. Catface. Anyway, call me, call me back.
我该怎么脱离这种困境
How do I get out of this?